{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039693310","data":{"timestamp":" 947039693310"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_65_81-65-70"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 65"," userResponse":" 70"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039699728","data":{"timestamp":" 947039699728"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_65_81-65-70"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 65"," userResponse":" 65"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039713936","data":{"timestamp":" 947039713936"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_66_66-60-86"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 66"," userResponse":" 66"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039723227","data":{"timestamp":" 947039723227"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_63_56-82-63"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 63"," userResponse":" 63"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039731039","data":{"timestamp":" 947039731038"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_82_82-50-55"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 82"," userResponse":" 82"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039743460","data":{"timestamp":" 947039743460"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_73_73-102-105"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 73"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039754284","data":{"timestamp":" 947039754284"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_73_73-106-70"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 73"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039762435","data":{"timestamp":" 947039762435"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_80_80-73-100"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 80"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039769627","data":{"timestamp":" 947039769627"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_80_80-73-100"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 80"," userResponse":" 80"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039778930","data":{"timestamp":" 947039778930"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_93_74-83-93"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 93"," userResponse":" 93"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039789037","data":{"timestamp":" 947039789037"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 97"," userResponse":" 96"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039796255","data":{"timestamp":" 947039796255"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 97"," userResponse":" 92"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039806578","data":{"timestamp":" 947039806578"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_97_96-97-92"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 97"," userResponse":" 97"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039830017","data":{"timestamp":" 947039830017"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 70"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039836935","data":{"timestamp":" 947039836934"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053424"," gameId":" 8f88328e-76c3-417d-bb44-7df2a1321241"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}